qusec.in 2015-04-12

# Privacy Policy

PLEASE READ THESE QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES PRIVACY POLICY AND RULES CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE. THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND RULES GOVERN YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE LOCATED AT www.Qusec.in, AND ARE APPICABLE TO ANY AND ALL SERVICES OFFERED www.Qusec.in THROUGH OTHER MEANS (like widgets/gadgets/api/products).

**Privacy Policy Purpose**

We respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding your personally identifiable information or “personal information” from unauthorized use or disclosure. This policy describes how your personal information may be collected when you visit our website, shop at our stores, use our products or access our services, enroll in our loyalty card program, or otherwise interact with us. It also describes how your personal information is used or disclosed and the steps we take to protect it from unauthorized use or disclosure. For special offers, promotions, contests or specific services, such as those provided by our pharmacies, we might advise you that additional or different personal information practices or terms exist. You should refer to those terms or practices as well.

**CONSENT TO PRIVACY POLICY**

By accessing our website to shop or obtain information or services, enrolling in our loyalty card program or providing personal information to us through other means, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**DEFINITION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We define the term “personal information” to mean any information that we directly associate with or use to identify a specific person. This may include an address, phone number, email address, fax number, or information pertaining to a rewards program, online registration or financial account, when associated with a person’s name. Our definition does not include "aggregate personal information,” which is information that we collect about a group or category of persons or services, or “de-identified information,” which is information from which we or our agents have removed any information that can be used to specifically identify a person, and this policy does not restrict or limit our collection or use of those types of information.

**Scope of Policy**

This policy applies to QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES treatment of personally identifiable information that QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES collects through QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES site and when you use QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES services. The policy does not apply to practices of companies whose Websites may be linked to QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES. For access to the privacy policies of such linked Websites please refer to the information provided by such Websites at their home pages. Also see the paragraph below under the heading "Hypertext Links".

QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES respects your privacy. Accordingly, it has adopted the following privacy policy.

**This policy notifies you of:**

-what personally identifiable information of yours is collected from you through our Website;

-the organization collecting the information;

-how the information is used;

-with whom the information may be shared;

-what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;

-the kind of procedures we employ in an effort to hinder the unauthorized access, deletion, alteration, use or disclosure of information you provide to QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES;

And

-how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information you provide to us.

**Information Collection and Use**

QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES may at times collect personally identifiable information. On such occasions, QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES may ask for your name, email address, zip code and personal information concerning your interests, occupation, gender and other demographic information. QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES also receives and records information from server logs from your browser including cookie information relating to pages requested and the like. QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES does not seek to collect such information from persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any such information to us. If you are the parent or guardian of a person under the age of 18 who has provided such information to us, please inform us (through the Website or address listed above) and we will remove such information from our database as described further below. In addition, no person (of any age) is required to provide us with the personally identifiable information we request. If you do not wish to provide such information, you are free not to do so. Your provision of requested information to us through our Website or other means is presumed by us to be voluntary and with your consent to the uses described herein. If after submitting personally identifiable information to us, you wish to "opt-out," please contact us as noted above and we will remove your information from our database as set forth below in the section titled "Managing Your Information." Please know that such a decision will not stop advertising or content that is generated prior to the time when we can accomplish the removal of your information. QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES uses the information you provide to us to customize content that we present to you, to contact you concerning specials and new products, to offer news and newsletters, and to enhance our product offering. QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to any third party except when: -You have been given an opportunity to "opt out" of sharing the information and have declined to exercise that right within the time period provided; - QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES must share the information in order to provide a product or service that you have requested, in which case we will demand that any third party we use to fulfill your order agree that it does not have the right to use the personally identifiable information other than to fulfill your request; or - QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES is required to respond to subpoena, court orders or other legal process requiring such disclosure.

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to any individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences while you’re at our site. The use of cookies is an industry standard—you’ll find them at most major websites. By showing how and when guests use the site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. If you accept the first tracking cookie from Buy Easy Be Busy, you won’t be offered as many afterwards. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Buy Easy Be Busy does not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to the Buy Easy Be Busy cookies policy. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you’d prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the site, like the shopping areas, will not function properly if you do so.

**Managing Your Information**

You are entitled to request access to and correction of all your personal data collected by us via this Website, as well as to require us to delete your data if you no longer want us to process it. You can make such a request or a related inquiry by emailing us at info@Qusec.in Please note that there may be a small charge for making an access request or it may be free, depending on the circumstances. You can find out more details by emailing us as provided above. We will keep your data as long as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and Rules. You may choose not to receive unsolicited marketing material from us and you have the right to request deletion of your Buy Easy Be Busy account information, subject to QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES need to keep appropriate archives of its business operations.

**About IP Addresses**

QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES reserves the right to collect your IP addresse(s) for the purposes of system administration and security reasons. An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Web. Web servers—the big computers that “serve” up Web pages—automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When guests request pages from Buy Easy Be Busy, our servers log their IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user’s session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us.

**Security**

QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES employs reasonable measures to maintain all personally identifiable information provided by you on computer servers in a controlled and secured environment in an effort to hinder unauthorized access, loss, alteration, use or disclosure of such information. However, the nature of the Internet is such that information may be transmitted over networks without appropriate security measures and may be accessed, deleted, altered, used or disclosed by unauthorized persons. Because of the international nature of the services and products provided by this Website and the nature of QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES's business, personal data may, subject to applicable law, be transferred internationally throughout the world (details of which are available on request by emailing or calling us as provided above) for the purposes described above. This may mean that personal data are transferred to countries which do not have laws or regulations which protect personal data, such as the United States, where the server for this Website is located. We use reasonable measures to limit the disclosure of the data you provide to us only to certain staff within QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES and its affiliates (i.e. staff whose job it is to process your inquiries and survey answers or otherwise to administer the Website, and those staff involved in the provision of QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES services and products which may be of interest to you) and to require that they process the data only for the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy and Rules.

**Modifications to this Policy**

QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES may make modifications or amendments to this policy from time to time. In the event that such changes alter how QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES gathers, processes, uses or discloses your personally identifiable information, QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES will post such changes on our site.

**Hypertext Links**

This site may contain hypertext links to websites that are not created or maintained by QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES. This Privacy Policy and Rules applies only to this Website and not to any of these third party websites. QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES is not responsible for the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, or completeness of those third party websites. The inclusion of any link to such websites does not imply endorsement, sponsorship, or recommendation by QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES of the site. QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES disclaims any liability for links

(1) from another website to www.Qusec.in and

(2) to another website from www.Qusec.in

QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES cannot guarantee the standards of any website to which links are provided on this site nor shall QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES be held responsible for the contents of non- QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES websites, or any subsequent links. For this reason, QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES does not represent or warrant that the contents of any third party website is accurate, compliant with state or central law, or compliant with copyright or other intellectual property laws. QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES does not endorse the contents of these third party websites in any way. Also, QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES is not responsible for web casting or any other form of transmission received from any linked website. Any reliance on the contents of a third party Website is done at your own risk and you assume all responsibilities and consequences resulting from such reliance. By using this website, you signify your assent to the QUSEC RETAIL VENTURES Privacy Policy and Rules. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the site.

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of www.Qusec.in following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

**How to Contact Us**

www.Qusec.in is controlled and operated by QUSEC RETAILVENTURES. Please forward any comments or complaints or any questions regarding privacy to “info@Qusec.in”.

Contact details

•           Customer Care: 080 6700 6969

•           Email: info@qusec.in
